Guide to the Robert A. Hill Collection, 1890-2014 RL.10993
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research (RE), 1889-2012 and undated; 10
  - General, 1
    - Father Raphael, 1913 (Box RE115)
    - Publications, 1913-1914 (Box RE115)
    - Jamaica Patriotic League, 1914 (Box RE115)
    - Improving 606, 1912 (Box RE115)
    - American monopolies, 1914 (Box RE115)
    - Bain Acues, 1912 (Box RE115)
    - Lightbourne, Rev. Arthur F., 1914 (Box RE115)
    - Young Men's Guild, Kingston, 1909 (Box RE115)
    - Wilcox, Ella Wheeler, 1912 (Box RE115)
    - U.S. and Liberia, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Education, 1913 (Box RE115)
    - Layman's League, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Radway, S.P., 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Solomon, George, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Universal Races, Congress, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Brer' Anansi, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Clerk, Asiley, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Jamaican missionaries to Africa, 1912 (Box RE115)
    - Jamaica Times, 1913 (Box RE115)
    - Jamaica Times, 1914; 2 folders (Box RE115)
    - Jamaica Times, 1915 (Box RE115)
    - Heuman - The Killing Time: The Morant Bay Rebellion in Jamaica, 1994 (Box RE115)
    - Hall - Among the Jamaican Negroes, 1902 (Box RE115)
    - Huxley - Race in Europe, 1944-1945 (Box RE115)
    - UNIA Motto, 1921 (Box RE115)
    - Name of UNIA source, undated (Box RE115)
    - Parker, George Wells - When Africa Awakes, 1919 (Box RE115)
    - WWI willingness to fight, 1914, 1919 (Box RE115)
    - A.P. Randolph - Our Only Way to Redeem Africa, undated (Box RE115)
    - Black Star Line, 1919, 1926 (Box RE115)
    - Randolph, A. Phillip, 1922 (Box RE115)
    - Roosevelt, 1918 Mar (Box RE115)
    - NIG - Educated and Thoughtful of Own Race, 1918 (Box RE115)
    - NIG - UNIA and ACL of JA, 1917 Jul (Box RE115)
    - Professor Garvey New York, 1917 (Box RE115)
    - Harlem Home News, 1917 Dec (Box RE115)
    - Return to Jamaica, 1911-1912 (Box RE115)
    - Anderson - Nation-State Cast in Imperial Mould, undated (Box RE115)
    - Kramer, Paul, undated (Box RE115)
    - Sedra - Imagining an Imperial Race, 2004 (Box RE115)
    - Marcus Garvey: Lectures, 1914 (Box RE115)
    - Marcus Garvey: WWI Impact, 1921-1923 (Box RE115)
    - Marcus Garvey: Travel to U.S., 1916 (Box RE115)
    - Marcus Garvey: Pauper's Grave, 1917-1919 (Box RE115)
    - Marcus Garvey: West Indies in U.S., 1916-1917 (Box RE115)
    - Chomsky, Aviva, 1995 (Box RE115)
    - Limóns Strike, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Putnam - The Company They Kept, undated (Box RE115)
    - Warehani, Jacob, 1909-1912 (Box RE115)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Reflections on the 1st of August, 1910 (Box RE115)
    - Rogers, J. A. - Marcus Garvey: Provisional President of Africa, undated (Box RE115)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Political Ambitions, 1905 (Box RE115)
    - BSL - Daily Transaction Report, 1920 Jan (Box RE115)
    - Powell, Fred D., 1919 Dec (Box RE115)
    - Hodge, Kirhorn - Foreign Neighbors, 1920 (Box RE115)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Serial Story on the Black Star Line Corp, 1922 Jan (Box RE115)
    - Wells, Ida B., 1916 (Box RE115)
    - Ovington, Marcus Garvey, 1927 (Box RE115)
    - Plain Talk, 1936-1938 (Box RE115)
    - Beverly Hamilton on Marcus Garvey, undated (Box RE115)
    - Ulotrochian, 1855-1840 (Box RE115)
    - Caribbean Series unsorted research, undated (Box RE115)
    - Malaya, 1919, 1943 (Box RE115)
    - Pan-African Congress, 1919 (Box RE115)
    - Joint Legislative Committees, Commissions, and Task Forces, 2009 (Box RE116)
    - African Telegraph, 1919 (Box RE116)
    - Smith, Rev. Charles S., 1921, undated; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Race Riots, 2005 (Box RE116)
    - Holsey, Albon Lewis, undated (Box RE116)
    - Brown, Rev. Ethelred, 1923 (Box RE116)
    - Robes of Many Colors, 1920 Aug 14 (Box RE116)
    - Richmond Planet, 1921 Feb (Box RE116)
    - Walrond, Eric, 1923 (Box RE116)
    - Half Century Magazine, 1921 Jan (Box RE116)
    - Bond, Horace Mann, 2010 (Box RE116)
    - Johnson, Growing up in the Black Belt, 1941 (Box RE116)
    - Cronon, 1955 (Box RE116)
    - White newspaper coverage of Marcus Garvey and the Black Star Line, 1920 (Box RE116)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Dispersion, 1913-1920 (Box RE116)
    - Malliet - UNIA Peak, 1919-1923, 1920, 1940 (Box RE116)
    - Malliet - A.M. Wendell, 1922-1928 (Box RE116)
    - Negro World - West Indian Emigration, Oct 1920 (Box RE116)
    - White Press, 1921 (Box RE116)
    - Scott, James - Disembedding, undated (Box RE116)
    - Standing, T.G. - Nationalism in Negro Leadership, undated (Box RE116)
    - Schuyler, George, 1920 Aug (Box RE116)
    - Elmes, Ruby - Garvey and Garveyism, 1925 May (Box RE116)
    - Walton, Lester, 1925 Apr, 2010; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - New York Globe, 1919 Nov 1 (Box RE116)
    - Frazier, E. Franklin, 1926, 2010; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - After Garvey?, 1925 Feb (Box RE116)
    - Brown/Pickens, 1926 (Box RE116)
    - Johnson, Charles S. - After Garvey - What?, 1924-1928 (Box RE116)
    - Miller, Kelly, 1925 (Box RE116)
    - Speeches by Garvey, 1920-1924 (Box RE116)
    - Alexander Gumby Collection newspaper clippings, 1924 Nov-Dec (Box RE116)
    - Dossen, James J., 1919 (Box RE116)
    - Perry, Rufus - Cushites, undated (Box RE116)
    - Bird, J.H. Dr., 1983 (Box RE116)
    - UNIA in Cleveland, Ohio, 1922 (Box RE116)
    - Grey, Edward M., 1927 (Box RE116)
    - Patsides, Nicholas - Marcus Garvey and Black Americans, 2007 (Box RE116)
    - Hahn, Steven, 2009 (Box RE116)
    - Rolinson, 2006 (Box RE116)
    - Newport News, 1919 Oct (Box RE116)
    - Hampton Roads, Virginia, 2010 (Box RE116)
    - Woodruff, Nan Elizabeth - American Congo, 2003 (Box RE116)
    - Negro World - Start a Branch, 1921 Feb (Box RE116)
    - Missouri - Jamaican Dentist, undated (Box RE116)
    - Ferris, William H. - Aladdin's Lamp, 1920 (Box RE116)
    - Moses, Wilson - The Golden Age of Black Nationalism, undated (Box RE116)
    - Burkett, Randall, 1978 (Box RE116)
    - Vincent, Theodore, undated; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Mays, Benjamin, 1971 (Box RE116)
    - Levine, Lawrence W., 1982 (Box RE116)
    - Stein, Judith, 1986, undated; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Harold, Claudrena, 2010 (Box RE116)
    - Mintz, Sidney - The Caribbean Region, undated (Box RE116)
    - Mazower, Mark, undated (Box RE116)
    - Ottley, Roi, 1993 (Box RE116)
    - Myrdal, Gunnar - An American Dilemma, 1944 (Box RE116)
    - Franklin, John Hope, 1947 (Box RE116)
    - Brisbane, Robert H., 1951, 1970; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Record, Wilson, 1954 (Box RE116)
    - Martin, Tony, 1976, undated; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Du Bois, W.E.B. - The UNIA, 1923 Jan (Box RE116)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Nativism, 1922 (Box RE116)
    - Bu Bois, W.E.B. - Black Star Line, 1922 Sep (Box RE116)
    - Garvey, Marcus - Playing the Color Game, 1921 (Box RE116)
    - Harris, Abram L. - Garvey, 1923 Jun (Box RE116)
    - Rogers, J.A. - Marcus Garvey Trial, 1923 (Box RE116)
    - Rogers, J.A. - interview, 1926 Nov (Box RE116)
    - Hancock, Gordon C. Dean - Virginia Union University, 1922 Mar (Box RE116)
    - Star of Zion - The Garvey Movement and the Negro in America, 1921 8 Sep (Box RE116)
    - Pickens, W., 1921 (Box RE116)
    - Messenger, 1922 Jul (Box RE116)
    - McKay - Garvey as a Negro Moses, undated (Box RE116)
    - White, Lucien B., 1922 Oct 21 (Box RE116)
    - Lawton, Charles C., 1922 Oct (Box RE116)
    - Owen, Chandler, 1923 Feb (Box RE116)
    - Garvey on Seligman and Du Bois, 1921-1923 (Box RE116)
    - Du Bois, W.E.B. and Marcus Garvey, 1923 (Box RE116)
    - Mitchell, Uriah, 2010 (Box RE116)
    - DuBois - Back to Africa, 1923 (Box RE116)
    - Wittner, Lawrence S. - The National Negro Congress: A Reassessment, 1970 (Box RE116)
    - Tolstoi, Leo, undated (Box RE116)
    - Reeves, Sir Conrad, undated (Box RE116)
    - Pacific Coast Negro Improvement Association, 1921 (Box RE116)
    - Norris, James Austin, 1928-1929 (Box RE116)
    - Harrison, Byron P. Senator, 1971 (Box RE116)
    - Chevannes, Barry, 1977, 1991 (Box RE116)
    - Pemberton III, John, 2000 (Box RE116)
    - Cook, Stephen L., 1995 (Box RE116)
    - Ermarth, Michael, 1978 (Box RE116)
    - Lentz, Linda, 2004 (Box RE116)
    - Lease, Gary, 2000 (Box RE116)
    - Stromberg, Peter, 1981, 1990-1991, 1998-2001; 5 folders (Box RE116)
    - Penner, Hans H., 2000 (Box RE116)
    - Braun, Will, 2000 (Box RE116)
    - Rouse-Jones, Margaret, 2007 (Box RE116)
    - Besson, Jean, 1996, 1998; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Kearney, Michael, 1975, 1984; 2 folders (Box RE116)
    - Smart, Ninian, 1983 (Box RE116)
    - Carrette, Jeremy, 1999 (Box RE116)
    - Sowande, Fela, 1974 (Box RE116)
    - Lewin, Olive, 1974 (Box RE116)
    - Dougherty, Janet, 1981 (Box RE116)
    - Riesebrodt, Martin, 1999 (Box RE116)
    - Olsen, Marvin, 1992 (Box RE116)
    - Silva, Francisco, 2004 (Box RE116)
    - Vasina, 1990 (Box RE116)
    - Macmillan, 1938 (Box RE116)
    - Hodgkin, Thomas, 1951, 1956; 4 folders (Box RE116)
    - Andaya, Barbara, 1996 (Box RE116)
    - Twaddle, Michael, 1971 (Box RE116)
    - Emerson, Rupert, 1965 (Box RE116)
    - Perham, Margery, 1936 (Box RE116)
    - McKay, Vernon, 1948 (Box RE116)
    - Shepperdson, George, 1952 (Box RE116)
    - South Africa Report, 1922 (Box RE116)
    - Lonsdale, John, 1993 (Box RE116)
    - Langley, J. Ayo, 1979 (Box RE116)
    - Legal Cases, 1919-1932 (Box RE116)
    - Abbreviations, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Addams, Jane, 1919 Jan 25 (Box RE117)
    - Adjutant Generals Department, 1920 (Box RE117)
    - Air Service Military Aeronautics, 1949 (Box RE117)
    - Davis, John W. - American Ambassador to Great Britain, undated (Box RE117)
    - Armenian Massacre, 1983 Apr 23-May 31 (Box RE117)
    - Anderson, Charles Williams, 1921, 1923, 1929 (Box RE117)
    - Baker, J.A., 1919 Dec 30 (Box RE117)
    - Baldwin, Roger, 1918-1919 (Box RE117)
    - Bannerman, Albert C., 1927-1960 (Box RE117)
    - Barclay, Colville, 1930 (Box RE117)
    - Battle, George Gorden, 1925, 1930, 1943-1950 (Box RE117)
    - Baum, George Martin, 1949 Oct 4 (Box RE117)
    - Berenberg, David Paul, 1972 (Box RE117)
    - Bickett, Thomas Walter, 1918 (Box RE117)
    - Blatchford Jr., William W., 1928 Jul (Box RE117)
    - British Delegation to the Peace Conference, 1978 (Box RE117)
    - Brownies Book, 1920 Oct (Box RE117)
    - Brown, Wrisley, 1919, 1924-1925 (Box RE117)
    - Bubler, Joseph S., 1945, 1961, 1977 (Box RE117)
    - De Bustamante, Antonio Sanchez, 1919, 1925-1939 (Box RE117)
    - Campbell, John B., 1945 Dec 14 (Box RE117)
    - Cardwell, Edward, undated (Box RE117)
    - Chamberlin, George E., 1916, 1921, 1924 (Box RE117)
    - Christian Science Monitor, 1920 Sep 1 (Box RE117)
    - Church of England, 1948, 1978 (Box RE117)
    - Clark, James E., 1945, 1952; 2 folders (Box RE117)
    - Clementi, Sir Cecil, 1937 (Box RE117)
    - Colson, Lt. William N., 1919, 1925, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Congressional Election, 1918 Nov 5 (Box RE117)
    - Coxe, Alexander B., 1980 Mar (Box RE117)
    - Creighton, John T., 1919-1921 (Box RE117)
    - Dalrymple, William Earl, 1919 Aug 31 (Box RE117)
    - D'Annuncio, Gabrielle, 1919-1920, 1938 (Box RE117)
    - Archbishop of Canterbury/Davidson, Randall T., 1978 (Box RE117)
    - De Cardi, Charles Count, 1906-1907 (Box RE117)
    - Demobilization, undated (Box RE117)
    - Dixon, Thomas, 1906 (Box RE117)
    - Dockerty, Alexander M., 1919, 1921 (Box RE117)
    - Dutasta, Paul Eugene, 1919-1920, 1924-1926 (Box RE117)
    - Elizabeth, Queen, undated (Box RE117)
    - Federal Bar Association, 1980 Mar 12 (Box RE117)
    - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, 1974 (Box RE117)
    - Ford, Robert, 1918-1919 (Box RE117)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1922-1972 (Box RE117)
    - The Freeman, 1942 May (Box RE117)
    - French and Belgian Amendments to League of Nations Charter, 1919 Apr (Box RE117)
    - Gavin, John H., 1947 Jun 25 (Box RE117)
    - Truzenika, Golos, 1919-1920 (Box RE117)
    - Gompers, Samuel, 1976 (Box RE117)
    - Greely, Horace, 1872 Nov 30-Dec 5 (Box RE117)
    - Greene, George Ball, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Grey, Edward, 1929-1940 (Box RE117)
    - Grossman, Moses and William, 1925, 1931, 1937 (Box RE117)
    - Guilbaud, Tertullien, 1918 (Box RE117)
    - Guiton, Katie A., 1918-1919 (Box RE117)
    - Guy, Charles Lewis, 1925, 1931, 1935 (Box RE117)
    - Harcourt, Lewis, 1922-1930 (Box RE117)
    - Harpoon, 1904, 1920, 1942 (Box RE117)
    - Hayes, Carlton Joseph Huntley, 1922-1932, 1964 (Box RE117)
    - Hayes, Howard Wood, 1917, 1980 (Box RE117)
    - Heath, Perry Sanford, undated (Box RE117)
    - Hitchcock, Edward Bering, 1919, 1946, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Holder, W.S., 1907, 1921, 1978 (Box RE117)
    - Hugo, Francis M., 1918, 1931, 1980 (Box RE117)
    - Jews and Ukrainian Autonomy, 1919 (Box RE117)
    - Jews in Poland, undated (Box RE117)
    - Johnstone, Robert, 1941-1950 (Box RE117)
    - Kenyon, Frederic George, 1914, 1951-1960 (Box RE117)
    - Kerwin, Edwin J., 1932, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Lane, Charles E., 1919, 1927, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Latin American Labor Conference, 1918 Oct-Nov (Box RE117)
    - Lawyers, 1918, 1979 (Box RE117)
    - Love, Rev. J. Albert, 1888, 1971 (Box RE117)
    - Landon, Alfred, 1987 Oct (Box RE117)
    - Liberia and American miscellaneous shipping lines and companies, 1922 Dec-1923 Jul, 1985 (Box RE117)
    - Abraham Lincoln and Thomas Jefferson on Colonization, undated (Box RE117)
    - Blacks of London, 1929-1930 (Box RE117)
    - London places, 1983 (Box RE117)
    - Louis, Joe, 1949 (Box RE117)
    - Lynching, 1930 Feb-1931 Mar (Box RE117)
    - MacDonald, Malcolm, 1981 Jan 12 (Box RE117)
    - Man/Men, 1929-1932 (Box RE117)
    - Miller, Kelly on Marcus Garvey, 1927 (Box RE117)
    - Pasha, Nahas, 1981 (Box RE117)
    - National Academy of Science, 1983 (Box RE117)
    - Negro, legal definitions of, 1910 (Box RE117)
    - Negro Welfare Association, 1934, 1980 (Box RE117)
    - NY AGE Charges Against Marcus Garvey, 1926 Feb 20-27 (Box RE117)
    - New York individuals, research, 1986 Jan 8-27 (Box RE117)
    - New York City rental increases, 1917, 1920, 1922 (Box RE117)
    - Numbers (Gambling), 1924 Aug 23-1931 Apr 18 (Box RE117)
    - Olivares, José de, 1925 Mar (Box RE117)
    - Olivier, 1908-1914, 1929-1942, 1969 (Box RE117)
    - Owen, Chandler, 1919-1923, 1927-1934, 1944-1967 (Box RE117)
    - Antonio Paez, International Negro Improvement Association, 1930 Oct 23-1931 Feb 13 (Box RE117)
    - Perkins, Frances, 1965 May 15 (Box RE117)
    - Petition to Pope and Archbishop UNIA Meeting, 1924 Sep 20 (Box RE117)
    - Philadelphia Tribune, 1984 Oct (Box RE117)
    - Railroads, 1926, 1937 (Box RE117)
    - Riots, U.S., 1926 (Box RE117)
    - Robertson, W.C., 1937 Jun 29 (Box RE117)
    - Rockefeller, John D., 1937 May 24-25 (Box RE117)
    - FDR Franklin D. Roosevelt and the New Deal, 1934 Jan-1945 Apr (Box RE117)
    - Rumble, Robert PNP, 1980 Apr 6 (Box RE117)
    - Scottsboro Boys defense, 1930 May 31-1936 Apr 28, 1983 (Box RE117)
    - Savory, Philip, 1950, 1965 Jun 12-19 (Box RE117)
    - Schoen, Julian A., 1926 (Box RE117)
    - Scopes' Evolution Trial, 1925 Jul 13, 1931, 1965-1984 (Box RE117)
    - Selfridge, Gordon, 1947 May 9 (Box RE117)
    - Simpson, Magistrate George, 1951 Aug 18 (Box RE117)
    - Stubbs, Governor R. Edward, Jamaica, 1941-1950 (Box RE117)
    - Survey graphic, Harlem issue of, 1925 Mar (Box RE117)
    - Terry, Watt, 1961 Apr 6 (Box RE117)
    - Tobias, David E., 1925 Dec-1926 Jan (Box RE117)
    - Trone, Solmon, 1932-1965, 1990, 1991; 2 folders (Box RE117)
    - Tut, King, 1922 (Box RE117)
    - United Trust Strike, 1929 May 12-1930 Jun 7 (Box RE117)
    - Universal Ethiopian Hymnal, 1922 (Box RE117)
    - USSR and Afro-Americans, 1932 Oct 20 (Box RE117)
    - Waison, Leonard P., 1930-1932 (Box RE117)
    - Wallis, Charles Braithwaite, undated (Box RE117)
    - Walker, Madam, 1916-1919, 1931, 1940-1987 (Box RE117)
    - Walker, Maggie L., 1924 Jul 20 (Box RE117)
    - Ward Theater, Kingston, 1923 Apr 6, 1985, 1986 (Box RE117)
    - W.A.S.U., Africa and the New Negro, 1929 Jan (Box RE117)
    - Wells, H.G., 1921 Dec 17 (Box RE117)
    - Who's Who on Colored America Index, 1927 (Box RE117)
    - Wilcox, Ella Wheeler, 1919, 1937 (Box RE117)
    - Woman, Women, 1919 Apr 20-1933 Jul 31 (Box RE117)
    - Bryan, William Jennings, 1917-1925, 1967-1969, 1980-1983 (Box RE118)
    - Bullard, Eugene, 1919 Jun (Box RE118)
    - Burke, Frank, 1917-1928, 1942, 1943 (Box RE118)
    - Burleson, Albert Sidney, 1920 Oct, 1937 Nov. 25 (Box RE118)
    - Burrell, Ben, 1921, 1944-1953, 1980 (Box RE118)
    - Bustamante, Sir Alexander, 1977 Apr 12 (Box RE118)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1924, 1934, 1983 (Box RE118)
    - Byrnes, Senator James F., 1919 Oct (Box RE118)
    - Cadet, Elizabeth, 1918-1920, 1979, 1982 (Box RE118)
    - Cargil, Henry Richard, undated (Box RE118)
    - Carpetner, Clarence Alex, 1922, 1979, 1980 (Box RE118)
    - Censorship Board, 1933, 1979 Jul (Box RE118)
    - Certain, Jeremiah, 1921, 1923 (Box RE118)
    - Champion Magazine, 1919 Dec, 1920 Jan (Box RE118)
    - Chicago Defender, 1915 Sep, 1919 Dec, 1923 Dec (Box RE118)
    - Chicago Riots, 1919, 1984 (Box RE118)
    - Churchill, Marlborough, 1925-1940, 1947 Jul 16 (Box RE118)
    - Norman, Julia Colman - Circle for Negro War Relief, undated (Box RE118)
    - Collins, Cornelius F., 1947 Feb 24 (Box RE118)
    - Colonial Office, 1901 May 1, 1979 Oct (Box RE118)
    - Colorado African Colonization Co., 1910 Jun 8 (Box RE118)
    - Communist Party, Great Britain, Anti-Colonialism, 1945 Apr 24 (Box RE118)
    - Connolly, W.T., 1979 Feb 21, Mar 28 (Box RE118)
    - Conventions, 1921 Jul (Box RE118)
    - Conway, Walter Johnson, 1979 (Box RE118)
    - Cotter interview, 1886-1887, 1903-1906 Mar, 1912 (Box RE118)
    - Cotterell, Arthur H.O., undated (Box RE118)
    - Craig, Arthur Ulysses, 1915, 1918 May 3, 1919 Sep 3 (Box RE118)
    - Crawley, George A., 1979 Jul 12 (Box RE118)
    - Cundall, Frank, 1946 (Box RE118)
    - Cutler, James Elbert, 1918, 1919, 1978 (Box RE118)
    - Daly, Victor, 1921 May, 1948 (Box RE118)
    - Dartiguenave, Philippe Sudre, 1915, 1920, 1921 (Box RE118)
    - Daugherty, Harry Micajah, 1921, 1975 (Box RE118)
    - Davis, James, 1994 Sep 8 (Box RE118)
    - Davis, Mortimer, 1925 Feb 2, 1917 Jul 19 (Box RE118)
    - Dempsey, Jack, 1923 Jul (Box RE118)
    - Dillon, John T., 1950 (Box RE118)
    - Dosmu-Johnson, T., 1933, 1937 (Box RE118)
    - Dolphin, Henry D., 1917, 1941, 1979 (Box RE118)
    - Debs, Eugene Victor, 1919-1926, 1976, 1982-1983 (Box RE118)
    - Dempsey, Jack, 1983 Jun 2 (Box RE118)
    - Domingo, W. A., 1918-1930, 1937-1944, 1952-1983; 4 folders (Box RE118)
    - The Emancipator, 1920 (Box RE118)
    - Dorsinville, H., 1920-1929, 1942, 1979 (Box RE118)
    - Douglas, Stephen Henry, undated (Box RE118)
    - Drake, Sir Francis, undated (Box RE118)
    - DuBois, W. E. B., 1903-1914, 1918-1938, 1957-1985 (Box RE118)
    - DuBois, W.E.B. - The Souls of Black Folk, 1903-1939, 1951-1986; 3 folders (Box RE118)
    - DuBois, W.E.B. - The Crisis, 1919 Jun-1932 Oct (Box RE118)
    - DuBois, W.E.B., 1903-1904, 1908-1919 (Box RE118)
    - Dumar, Rev. Alphonse, 1914 Oct 14, 1924 Jun 14 (Box RE118)
    - Duncan, Samuel A., 1918-1921, 1924, 1980 (Box RE118)
    - Durie, Walter, 1933 Jul 1-1933 Jul 17 (Box RE118)
    - Garvey, Amy Jacques, 1927 Sep 17 (Box RE118)
    - Eason W. H., 1920 Aug 18 (Box RE118)
    - East St. Louis Riots, Reports of the Special Committee to the House of Reps., 1918 Jul 5 (Box RE118)
    - Edwards, James Josiah, undated (Box RE118)
    - Egypt, 1919 (Box RE118)
    - Emancipator, 1919 Oct-1920 Apr (Box RE118)
    - Emmet, Robert, 1972 (Box RE118)
    - The Epilepsies - Porter and Morselli, undated (Box RE118)
    - Epilepsy - Dr. Porter, 1985 Dec-1987 Dec (Box RE118)
    - Espionage Act, 1918-1919, 1960, 1974-1985 (Box RE119)
    - L'Essor, 1919 Aug (Box RE119)
    - American Exceptionalism, 1985 (Box RE119)
    - Fascism, 1943, 1986-1988 (Box RE119)
    - Faneuil Hall, Boston, 1920-1921 (Box RE119)
    - Fanning, Joseph P., 1919 Sep-1919 Oct. (Box RE119)
    - Farrell, Walter Napier, 1979 Jul 12 (Box RE119)
    - Fearing, Charles H., 1980 Apr. 28 (Box RE119)
    - Finch, R. W., 1919 Oct.-1920 Jan. (Box RE119)
    - Flanders Field, 1915 (Box RE119)
    - Flynn, William, 1921 Apr. 2 (Box RE119)
    - From Greenlano's Icy Mountains, 1903, 1926-1927, 1945-1946 (Box RE119)
    - Fuller, Charles - Garvey Film, 1973 Apr. (Box RE119)
    - Gandhi, 1925, 1932, 1981-1983 (Box RE119)
    - Marcus Garvey, A Reappraisal Symposium, 1987 Nov (Box RE119)
    - Marcus Garvey articles, 1920, 1968-1975 (Box RE119)
    - Marcus Garvey - charismatic leadership, 1981, 1989 (Box RE119)
    - Marcus Garvey, epilepsy - Lechtenberg, undated (Box RE119)
    - Marcus Garvey - illness, 1922-1925, 1935-1952, 1981-1984 (Box RE119)
    - Gaskill, Frank H., 1937 Aug 23 (Box RE119)
    - George, Albert B., 1915, 1924-1927, 1972-1979 (Box RE119)
    - German Propaganda Among Negroes in World War I, 1917, 1919 (Box RE119)
    - George, John M., undated (Box RE119)
    - Gideon, David Sampson, undated (Box RE119)
    - Gordon, Egbert T. Morris, 1920-1923, 1952-1979 (Box RE119)
    - Govin, Daniel, 1917 Sep 25 (Box RE119)
    - Graham, Wesley Faul, 1893-1902, 1952, 1980 (Box RE119)
    - Great Crisis of 1918-1921, 1920-1921, 1931 (Box RE119)
    - Great War and its Aftermath, 1981 (Box RE119)
    - Guatemala, 1982, 1986 (Box RE119)
    - Hall, Woosley W., 1964 Oct 22 (Box RE119)
    - Harding, Chester, 1911, 1917-1921, 1936-1937 (Box RE119)
    - Hawkins, John K., 1910-1918, 1921-1929, 1939-1948 (Box RE119)
    - Haynes, James, 1918, 1932 (Box RE119)
    - Henry, Patrick, 1775, 1975, 1983, 1986 (Box RE119)
    - Herald, Marcel, undated (Box RE119)
    - Hillquit, Morris, 1917 Nov 1934 (Box RE119)
    - Holsey, Albion Lewis, 1919 Jul 4, 1932 Mar 5, 1981 Feb 23 (Box RE119)
    - The Home News, 1977 (Box RE119)
    - Horton, James A., 1934 Feb-1939 Oct; 1946-1947, 1964 Mar (Box RE119)
    - House, Frederick B., 1925 (Box RE119)
    - Hunter, R. W., 1936 (Box RE119)
    - Immigration Laws, 1981 (Box RE119)
    - Intercolonial Steamship and Trading Company, 1920 (Box RE119)
    - I.W.W. and race riots, 1917-1919, 1921-1922 (Box RE119)
    - Irish Question in 1916, 1914-1920 (Box RE119)
    - Jackson, Anselmo R., 1918-1921 (Box RE119)
    - Japan's Racial Equality Proposal amendment, 1918-1921, 1971, 1975 (Box RE119)
    - Jenkins, James Francis, 1927 (Box RE119)
    - Jensen, Joan, 1978 (Box RE119)
    - Johnson, Edward Austin, 1918, 1928-1929, 1933-1944 (Box RE119)
    - Johnson, Gabriel, 1920 (Box RE119)
    - Johnson, Joseph Everett, 1918 Sep. 12 (Box RE119)
    - Johnson, James, 1890 (Box RE119)
    - Jonas, R.D., 1921, 1868-1918; 2 folders (Box RE119)
    - Jonas, J.W. Captain, 1888-1924, 1943-1967 (Box RE119)
    - Jordan, Rev. Hilton, 1981 (Box RE119)
    - Jordon, Professor Philip (Gordon), 1919, 1956 (Box RE119)
    - Kilnol, Edwin P., 1918-1925, 1940, 1953 (Box RE119)
    - Knight, Rev. B.A.C., undated (Box RE119)
    - Kornweibel, Theodore - No Crystal Stair, 1975 (Box RE119)
    - Kirowia, 1977 (Box RE119)
    - Lamar, William Harmung, 1913, 1918-1919, 1923-1928 (Box RE119)
    - Lansing, Robert, undated (Box RE119)
    - Larkin, James (Jim), 1919, 1923, 1969 (Box RE119)
    - Lazarus, Charles P., undated (Box RE119)
    - Law, Andrew Bonar, undated (Box RE119)
    - League of Nations, 1919 (Box RE119)
    - Lewis, William H., 1916 May, 1919 Mar (Box RE119)
    - Bruce, John E. and Love, Robert - correspondence, 1893-1899 (Box RE120)
    - Ludendorff, Erich, 1937 Dec 20 (Box RE120)
    - Masterlar, Kenneth C., 1918-1920, 1978-1980 (Box RE120)
    - Mends, Alfred A. - Jamaica Reform Club, 1922 Apr-1926 Mar (Box RE120)
    - Military abbreviations, 1931, 1949, 1979 (Box RE120)
    - Miner, Randolph Huntington, 1979-1980 (Box RE120)